A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Snapshot Files, RG 4 FA1128C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Miscellaneous (300), 1930-1989; 4
  - 300,050 JDR 3 Portrait, Artwork at 834 Fifth Ave, 1984 December (Box 10)
    Also includes unidentified man at frame shop; MFR by tree.
  - 300,051 Dogs, Flowers in Mexico, 1985 (Box 10)
    Disk negative; two prints.
  - 300,052 Flowers in Mexico, 1985-1985 (Box 10)
  - 300,053 Joan of Arc (Paris); Marymount and Kent House (Pocantico), 1985 May (Box 10)
    Negatives only.
  - 300,054 Princess Boncompagni and Flowers, circa 1985 (Box 10)
    Negative strip and disc negative only.
  - 300,054.1 Beaverkill, NY, and Leonard Firestone House in Aspen, 1985 Summer (Box 10)
  - 300,055 Black and White Photos not in Albums, circa 1930s - 1970s (Box 10)
    College football games; bar table; MFR? Golfing (black caddies); tennis game; unidentified woman on croquet lawn; Sea Star (1970s); Captain Tom Taxter and LSR on Chris Craft "commuter," ca. 1938; photo of gorilla Bobby, taken by Else Schneider of the Berlin Zoological Gardens, 1935; LSR, MFR, Hitchcocks and others, on sidewalk by beach, February 19, 1950; Dauntless and Tom Taxter; unidentified people; LSR and NAR with car in front of Hawes House (Saturday Evening Post).
  - 300,056 Miscellaneous, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 10)
    Blanchette; Paul Maze; various unidentified people; early resort photos (possibly Dorado; includes LSR, Allston Boyer)
  - 300,057 Unidentified views, 1940s or later (Box 10)
    Small black and white prints and negatives. Views of coastline.
  - 300,058 Unidentifed couple; LSR and MFR in Tour Group, Undated (Box 10)
    Two color prints.
  - 300,059 Unidentified Dinner occasion with MFR, Undated (Box 10)
  - 300,060 JY Ranch and Woodstock, Undated (Box 10)
    Includes print of LSR, MFR, and Mamdouha Bobst; Woodstock church; unidentified woman.
  - 300,061 Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 10)
    Polaroid of Christmas gifts LSR and MFR took to Japan; gardens in Maine; Mazes's dogs
  - 300,062 MFR at picnic with unidentified couple, Undated (Box 10)
    One print.
  - 300,063 MFR, Undated (Box 10)
    Polaroids. MFR at Kent House with two black labs; MFR at her desk.
  - 300,064 Miscellaneous Black and White, circa 1950s - 1970s (Box 10)
    MFR on boat; Happy Rockefeller and Jay Rockefeller; LSR and MFR with girl on pony (indoors?).
  - 300,065 Boats, 1970s (Box 10)
  - 300,066 MFR with Warren Weber and Hugh (their butler - deceased) (Box 10)
  - 300,067 Flowers, 1956 - 1970s (Box 10)
  - 300,068 Asian artwork; Gerald Ford speaking at National Park Service event, 1970s (Box 10)
  - 300,069 Moon (Box 10)
  - 300,070 Aircraft Carrier and Planes, circa 1940s (Box 10)
  - 300,071 New York City Skyline and River Views, Central Park Zoo, 1940s; later 1940 (Box 10)
    Black and white prints, and color polaroids.
  - 300,071.1 JDR Jr. Rockfeller Center Views, 1973 February (Box 10)
    John D. Rockefeller Jr., "I Believe" plaque. Color slides.
  - 300,072 Miscellaneous Polaroid Images, circa 1970s (Box 10)
    Includes Dauntless; MFR and others on carriage ride.
  - 300,073 LBJ Memorial Grove bridge; Hudson River views, 1977 October (Box 10)
  - 300,074 Resort Construction, 1960s (Box 11)
    Mauna Kea and other
  - 300,075 Sculpture in Garden (Maine), Undated (Box 11)
  - 300,076 Dr. Connie Guion, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 11)
    In red golf cart.
  - 300,077 Lincoln School Reunion, late 1940s-1950s (Box 11)
    Group photo.
  - 300,077.1 Lincoln School Reunion, 1988 (Box 11)
    Class of 1928 sixtieth reunion. Images presumably duplicates of those in 100,063 and 100,063.1.
  - 300,077.2 Lincoln School Reunion, 1988 (Box 11)
  - 300,077.3 Lincoln School Reunion, 1988 (Box 11)
    Class of 1928 sixtieth reunion. Negative strips.
  - 300,078 Lady Bird Johnson, 1983; undated (Box 11)
    Inscribed image of Lady Bird standing on Texas highway median planted with wildflowers, 1983; Lady Bird, Nash Castro, MFR, and others on unidentified occasion, in Vermont
  - 300,079 MFR and LSR at 834 Fifth Ave, 1984 December; undated (Box 11)
    LSR and MFR with unidentified couple, by branches decorated with silver moss; MFR with unidentified woman.
  - 300,080 Jessie Maze, 1969; 1978 (Box 11)
    Includes images of LSR and MFR.
  - 300,081 Paul and Jessie Maze, 1950s -1978 (Box 11)
    Paul and Jessie Maze, Mill Cottage, puppies.
  - 300,082 Miscellaneous People, 1930s-1970s (Box 11)
    LSR, MFR, and others. With Elizabeth Hitchcock, circa 1950; at resort, 1950s; with Lady Bird Johnson, 1974; Woodstock; etc.
  - 300,083 Miscellaneous People, circa 1950s-1980s (Box 11)
    Arthur Massola, Elizabeth Hitchcock, Millie Snowden, LSR and others at pool in Brazil, LSR with Leonard Firestone, Paul Maze daughter, Laetitia Boncompagni.
  - 300,084 Peter Paine, 1959 February (Box 11)
    LSR and MFR hunting with Peter Paine, Willsboro, NY.
  - 300,085 Rutherfurd, 1968 October - November (Box 11)
  - 300,086 Lowell Thomas, Undated (Box 11)
    One print. LSR and MFR with Lowell Thomas.
  - 300,087 Marion Weber Family, 1970 September (Box 23)
    One print of children.
  - 300,088 Bonsai trees (China); Artwork, 1985 November (Box 11)
  - 300,089 Dai Bosatsu Zendo, 1986 March (Box 11)
  - 300,090 New York Yacht Club, 1986 May (Box 11)
    LSR with Ethan Hitchcock, on occasion of LSR's donating Sea Star model to the New York Yacht Club.
  - 300,091 LBJ Ranch and Japanese Peace Garden, 1986 circa April (Box 11)
    Lady Bird Johnson with LSR, MFR, Nash and Bette Castro, and others. Two images from Nimitz Museum, Fredericksburg, TX.
  - 300,092 LBJ Ranch, 1986 circa April (Box 11)
  - 300,093 LBJ Ranch, 1986 circa April (Box 11)
  - 300,094 LBJ Ranch, 1986 circa April (Box 11)
    Folk art - museum visit
  - 300,095 LBJ Ranch, 1986 circa April (Box 11)
  - 300,095.1 LBJ Ranch, 1986 circa April (Box 11)
    Photos sent by Bette Castro.
  - 300,096 Princeton University - Rockefeller College Brunch, 1986 circa May (Box 11)
  - 300,097 Bogarts' Fiftieth Anniversary, 1986 circa May (Box 11)
  - 300,098 Spiritual Life Institute, Baca, Colorado, 1989 September (Box 11)
    LSR and MFR, Hanne Strong (Manitou Foundation), Crestone, CO.
- Civic (400), 1940-1990; 5
  - 400,000 Belgian Congo - Textile Plant, circa 1950s (Box 11)
  - 400,001 Aircraft Carrier - McDonnell Phantom Jets, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 11)
    Similar to prints in Envelope 300,070.
  - 400,002 Winston Churchill - Williamsburg Award Ceremony, 1955 December 7 (Box 11)
    Presentation of Williamsburg Award to Winston Churchill, Drapers Hall, London. Winthrop Rockefeller, chair of Colonial Williamsburg; Kenneth Chorley; and others.
  - 400,003 Lady Bird Johnson, Dedication of Billings Mansion as a National Historical Monument, 1967 June 11 (Box 11)
    LSR, MFR, Henry Diamond, and others. Also includes image of Lady Bird and all at Taftsville Bridge, and riding in antique car.
  - 400,003.1 South Pacific Conservatory, 1972 May (Box 11)
    Two slides- dance for LSR and MFR and cake.
  - 400,003.2 JDR Jr. Memorial Parkway Dedication, 1972 September 18 (Box 11)
    LSR speaking at dedication ceremony. One image.
  - 400,003.5 LBJ Memorial Grove and Fort Lee Historic Park, 1974 September; 1976 May (Box 11)
    Dedication ceremonies at the two parks. 3 images, sent by Nash Castro.
  - 400,003.7 Green Gulch Zen Center, 1977 March (Box 11)
    LSR and MFR at the center.
  - 400,004 National Park System Meeting at Kykuit, 1978 April (Box 11)
    Includes Secretary of the Interior Andrus, LSR, Nash Castro, and others.
  - 400,005 ACA and JHPI Board Members at JY Ranch, 1981 (Box 11)
    Includes images with identifications of Martha Hanson, Josephine Fabian, Holly Whyte, Jenny Bell Whyte, Mr. and Mrs. Russell Train, and Fred Smith. Also includes award to LSR and MFR from Friends of the Hospital, Jackson Hole.
  - 400,006 Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 November (Box 11)
    Event with King Carl XVI Gustaf and Queen Silvia of Sweden. LSR, MFR with Sam Babbitt, MSKCC.
  - 400,007 EAL Argentina Trip, 1982 November (Box 12)
    Horses and cattle.
  - 400,008 EAL Argentina Trip, 1982 November (Box 12)
    Photos sent by James A. Elkins, Jr. LSR and MFR on plane, cattle show.
  - 400,009 Transfer of Caneel Bay from JHPI to the National Park Service, 1983 September 13 (Box 12)
    LSR signing gift of land at Caneel Bay from Jackson Hole Preserve Inc. to the National Park Service, Virgin Islands National Park. Witnessed by Connie Wirth.
  - 400,010 Green Gulch Zen Center Tea House, 1984 November (Box 12)
    Photos of Japanese Tea House given by LSR to the Green Gulch Zen Center, Marin County, CA.
  - 400,011 Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, Nathan Cummings Center, circa 1984 - 1985 (Box 12)
    Include Cummings, LSR, Paul Marks, Benno Schmidt.
  - 400,012 Eastern Airlines - Rickenbacker Fountain and Silver Dove Award, 1985 March (Box 12)
    EAL, Miami. Award presented by LSR.
  - 400,013 Jackson Hole Preserve Board Meeting, 1960s (Box 12)
    Group photo at Jackson Lake Lodge.
  - 400,014 MFR USO "Woman of the Year" Award, 1985 May (Box 12)
  - 400,015 LSR and MFR at Woodstock Inn and with Ira Allen Award, 1985 June (Box 12)
    Prints and slide.
  - 400,016 LSR and MFR at University of Vermont and with Ira Allen Award, 1985 June (Box 12)
  - 400,017 LSR Rockefeller Center Office, 1980s; undated (Box 12)
    LSR desk and artwork - various images. Includes Caneel Bay pillow, Ruth Haupert, unidentified women. Snaphsot of LSR and MFR at Saratoga, sent by Richard E. Berlin 1960s?
  - 400,017.1 LSR Rockefeller Center Office, 1986 May (Box 12)
    Artwork
  - 400,018 Rockefeller Center Office Parties, 1978-1980s (Box 12)
    Fred Taylor retirement party, with JDR 3 and Blanchette; unidentified occasion with LSR, DR, Richard Parsons, and others.
  - 400,019 Dilworths and LSR, 1984 (Box 12)
    Mr. and Mrs J. Richardson Dilworth
  - 400,020 Ellen Leddy, 1984 July (Box 12)
    With LSR's bird, Chris. One print and disc negative.
  - 400,021 Montgomery Place and Edgewater, 1985 August (Box 12)
    Sleepy Hollow Restoration Project. Livingston House, Montgomery Place; Edgewater (Richard Jenrette, owner).
  - 400,022 Bassett Hall, 1985 November (Box 12)
    Interior shots, paintings, and bonsai.
  - 400,023 Missing photo, 1986 February 28 (Box 12)
    Celeste Senneur, LSR, Fred Smith, and Ruth Haupert at Room 5600. No images in envelope.
  - 400,024 Rockefeller State Park Preserve, 1986 circa May (Box 12)
    LSR, DR, Jay Rockefeller, Mario Cuomo at Rockefeller State Park Preserve ceremonies.
  - 400,025 Ronald Reagan at Kykuit, 1986 July (Box 12)
    LSR, MFR, Peggy Rockefeller, greeting Reagan, who stayed at Pocantico during the Statue of Liberty Centennial Celebration.
  - 400,026 LSR at Animal Medical Center dinner, 1986 (Box 12)
    Two images of LSR with unidentified women.
  - 400,027 Hospital Chaplaincy Dinner, 1986 November 6 (Box 12)
    LSR and MFR
  - 400,028 Thai Physicians Association, 1988 circa April (Box 12)
    LSR, MFR, DR, Peggy Rockefeller.
  - 400,029 Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center Murals, 1990 April (Box 12)
    MFR and other volunteers painting murals in tunnel at MSKCC.
  - 400,030 Paul Maze, LSR, and MFR in France, 1980s (Box 12)
- Travel (500), 1924-1989; 6
  - 500,000 MFR, circa 1940s (Box 12)
    Unidentified site - Jamaica
  - 500,001 Caribbean, circa 1940s (Box 12)
    MFR, bay views, donkeys, horses.
  - 500,002 Spain, Greece, Egypt, circa 1940s (Box 12)
    Bullfight; MFR in mountain scenery; Gibraltar?
  - 500,003 New York, circa 1940s (Box 12)
    New York shorelines; Dauntless.
  - 500,004 MFR, circa 1940s (Box 12)
    MFR on beach, and dining.
  - 500,005 Florida and Bahamas? Eastern Air Lines Board meeting?, 1940s (Box 12)
    Eastern Air Lines planes, board visit, MFR, scenery, horse racing, fishing, Eddie Rickenbacker.
  - 500,006 Boat- Sea Beast, circa 1940s (Box 12)
    MFR aboard the Sea Beast.
  - 500,007 Miscellaneous, circa 1940s - 1950s (Box 12)
    Essex, CT marina; shooting party - Everglades
  - 500,008 Miscellaneous, 1924; circa 1950s 1970s (Box 12)
    Includes various family and friends, LSR and MFR golfing; LSR speaking at unidentified event, Wildlife Conservation Society, Enid A. Haupt; postcard photo of Joseph Secakuku, Yellowfeet Tribe Hopi, circa 1924.
  - 500,008 (A) Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 23)
    Neva Kaiser letter to LSR, and enclosures.
  - 500,009 Unidentified Trip, 1975 May (Box 12)
    LSR, MFR, and Elizabeth French Hitchcock.
  - 500,010 Africa- Belgian Congo, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    Envelope marked, Sabena trip to Africa, Belgian Congo. Animals being unloaded for the New York Zoological Society. Includes Fairfield Osborn, MFR.
  - 500,011 Africa and New York, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    Ship approaching unidentified shore; MFR and others on cruise deck.
    One roll of negatives has been separated to box 25.
  - 500,012 Africa, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    Ship docking, MFR, road sign (Kano), animals (lion, zebra, primates), man with sewing machine.
    Three rolls of negatives (numbered 421, 434, and 435) have been separated to box 25.
  - 500,013 Africa, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    School, children, women, zoo, workers, scenery.
    Two rolls of negatives (numbered 424 and 427) have been separated to box 25.
  - 500,014 Africa, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    Farm, landscapes, villages, women, children, fishermen, animals, river, natives and unidentified white men and women; MFR at the equator.
    Two rolls of negatives (numbered 428 and 433) have been separated to box 25.
  - 500,015 Africa, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    Grassland wildlife (elephants, hippos, deer, birds, etc.); views, river, woman and child, MFR by ferry.
    Three rolls of negatives (numbered 425, 431, and 436) have been separated to box 25.
  - 500,016 Africa- Egypt, circa 1950s (Box 13)
    One image- Man on camel by pyramid and sphinx. Enlargement dated 1966.
  - 500,017 Africa- Egypt, circa 1950s (Box 13)
    MFR, LSR, and others. Views, river, pyramid, sphinx, Sabena plane, camels.
    Two rolls of negatives (numbered 422 and 467) have been separated to box 25.
  - 500,018 Europe, circa 1950s (Box 13)
    Views of unidentified castle and park grounds, MFR by fountain, view of cockpit of airplane.
    One roll of negatives (numbered 423) has been separated to box 25.
  - 500,019 Europe, circa 1956 October (Box 13)
    MFR and children on steps by scuplture; daughters on bench.
  - 500,020 Europe- Family Trip - Italy, 1958 (Box 13)
    MFR, LSR, and family; racecars and racetrack, street and country scenes, sculpture.
  - 500,021 Europe- Family Trip - Italy, 1958 (Box 13)
    Florence. Museums and art.
  - 500,022 Europe- Family Trip - Italy, 1958 (Box 13)
    Rome.
  - 500,023 Europe- Family Trip - Italy, 1958 (Box 13)
    Venice.
  - 500,024 Europe- Family Trip - France, Belgium, 1958 (Box 13)
    Includes 1958 World's Fair, Brussels.
  - 500,025 Europe- England, 1958 September (Box 13)
    Jessie Maze, with puppies.
  - 500,026 Europe, 1975 May (Box 13)
    Barge trip; sailing with Elizabeth and Ethan Hitchcock.
  - 500,027 Europe, 1975 May (Box 13)
    Barge trip. Prints and negatives.
  - 500,027.1 Europe, 1975 May (Box 13)
  - 500,028 Europe- England, 1979 May 8 (Box 13)
    Helicopter to Rolls-Royce Limited, Derby. One print.
  - 500,029 Europe- England and France, 1982 June (Box 13)
    Giverny, Rodin Museum, LSR, MFR, John French, Van der Kemps.
  - 500,030 Europe- England, circa 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - 500,031 Europe- England, 1984 May (Box 13)
  - 500,032 Europe- England, 1984 May (Box 13)
  - 500,033 Europe- England, 1984 May (Box 13)
  - 500,034 Europe- England, 1985 May (Box 13)
    Bath, American Museum.
  - 500,035 Europe- England, 1985 May (Box 13)
    Bath, LSR.
  - 500,036 Europe- England and France, 1985 May (Box 13)
  - 500,037 Europe- England, 1985 May (Box 13)
    Flower arrangements, Duke of York Hotel, Bath.
  - 500,038 Europe- England, 1985 May (Box 13)
    Monuments, London.
  - 500,039 Europe- France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    Visit with Etienne Maze in Burie, and La Rochelle.
  - 500,039.1 Europe- France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    Etienne Maze and La Rochelle.
  - 500,039.2 Europe- France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    La Rochelle.
  - 500,039.3 Europe- England and France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    Etienne and Margaret Maze, paintings.
  - 500,039.4 Europe- England and France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    France - market and street scenes. Maze visit.
  - 500,039.5 Europe- England and France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    LSR, MFR, England. Maze visit.
  - 500,039.6 Europe- England and France, 1983 May (Box 13)
    Mazes.
  - 500,040 Europe- France, 1984 May (Box 13)
  - 500,041 Europe - France, circa 1985 (Box 13)
    Musee Claude Monet; Gerald van der Kemp.
  - 500,041.1 Europe - France, 1985 (Box 13)
    Musee Claude Monet, Giverny; Gerald van der Kemp, LSR, MFR, John French; Jessie Maze.
  - 500,042 Europe- France, 1985 May (Box 13)
  - 500,042.1 Europe, circa 1985 (Box 13)
    Mazes, MFR, LSR, and others.
  - 500,043 Europe- Greece, 1979 (Box 14)
  - 500,044 Europe- Greece, 1979 (Box 14)
    MFR, LSR, Lady Bird Johnson, and others. On board ship.
  - 500,045 Europe- Italy, 1979 May (Box 14)
    Miscellaneous views.
  - 500,046 Europe- Norway, 1956 July (Box 14)
    MFR, also children. Paul Maze yard and painting.
  - 500,047 Europe- Norway, circa 1974 (Box 14)
    Views.
  - 500,048 Asia- Japan, circa 1962; 1970s (Box 14)
    LSR, MFR, and Larry R. in Kyoto; LSR and MFR and others, visiting museum.
  - 500,049 Mexico, circa 1981 (Box 14)
  - 500,049.1 Mexico, 1981 (Box 14)
  - 500,050 Mexico, 1981-1982 Spring (Box 14)
  - 500,051 Mexico, circa 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - 500,052 Mexico, 1984 (Box 14)
  - 500,053 Mexico, 1984 Spring (Box 14)
  - 500,054 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
  - 500,055 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
  - 500,056 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
  - 500,057 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
    LSR and MFR standing alongside inscriptions on ruins. Site unidentified.
  - 500,058 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
  - 500,059 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
  - 500,060 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
    Photos of world's largest tree.
  - 500,061 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
    Disk negatives only.
  - 500,062 Mexico, 1985 (Box 14)
  - 500,063 Mexico, 1985 April (Box 14)
    Peter Glenville, San Miguel.
  - 500,064 Mexico, 1985 April (Box 14)
  - 500,065 Mexico, 1985 April (Box 14)
  - 500,065.1 Mexico, 1986 (Box 14)
    Sheep and goats.
  - 500,066 USA- Alaska, 1960 August (Box 14)
    Includes LSR family.
  - 500,067 USA- Alaska, 1960 (Box 14)
  - 500,068 USA- Alaska, 1960 August (Box 14)
  - 500,069 USA- Alaska, 1960 August (Box 14)
  - 500,070 USA- Alaska, 1960 September (Box 14)
  - 500,071 USA- Alaska, 1960 September (Box 14)
  - 500,072 USA- Maine and Massachusetts, 1957 August (Box 14)
  - 500,073 USA- Maine, 1981 July (Box 14)
    Includes images from gardens.
  - 500,074 Empty, 1982 September (Box 14)
    Empty envelope, marked "U.S. - Maine." Note indicates that negatives are filed with 200,016.1.
  - 500,075 USA- Family Trip - West, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 500,076 USA- Family Trip - West, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 500,077 USA- Family Trip - West, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 500,078 USA- Family Trip - West, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 500,079 USA- Family Trip - West, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 500,080 USA- Family Trip - West, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 500,081 USA- Yellowstone, circa 1948 (Box 15)
  - 500,082 Caribbean, 1957 March 14 (Box 15)
    Note on envelope- "Visit to Sir Alan"
  - 500,083 Puerto Rico, 1957 April 22 (Box 15)
  - 500,084 Puerto Rico, 1957 April 22 (Box 15)
    Palomino Island (Bachmans). LSR family; Larry R. with monkey.
  - 500,085 USA- Provincetown and Cape Cod, MA (Box 15)
  - 500,086 USA- New York or Vermont, 1957 October 22 (Box 15)
    Golf and tennis. Two images.
  - 500,086.1 Mexico, 1959 (Box 15)
    Acapulco. LSR on pool deck (one image).
  - 500,087 Caribbean, 1965 March (Box 15)
    Trip on "Rara Avis." LSR, Hitchcocks.
  - 500,088 Caribbean and Hawaii, 1965 March (Box 15)
    Sailing ("Rara Avis") with Hitchcocks; one image of golf at Mauna Kea.
  - 500,089 South America, 1966 circa April (Box 15)
    YWCA trip. MFR, LSR, and others.
  - 500,090 Caribbean, 1965 March (Box 15)
  - 500,091 USA, 1971 September (Box 15)
    Happy Rockefeller, LSR, MFR, and unidentified others on plane; cattle; LSR at Billings Farm. Slides and prints.
  - 500,092 Fort Ticonderoga and England, 1976 May (Box 15)
  - 500,092.1 Europe- Spain, 1976 December (Box 15)
    Three images- unidentified women on plane.
  - 500,093 Union Pacific, Black Butte Dedication Special, 1979 (Box 15)
    Black Butte coal mine, Wyoming.
  - 500,094 Brooke Astor, St. Catherine's Island Trip, 1981 October 17 (Box 15)
    Includes artwork, NAR portrait, porcelains.
  - 500,095 USA- Vermont, 1981 (Box 15)
    Coolidge home, Woodstock mansion and grounds, Billings Farm, MFR and grandchildren.
  - 500,096 USA- Florida - Palm Beach, 1981 (Box 15)
    Woman and dog.
  - 500,097 USA- Hawaii, 1982 January (Box 15)
    Palm tree planting. Photos by Kenneth Brown.
  - 500,098 USA- New York, circa 1982 (Box 15)
    Boats in lot, Long Island.
  - 500,099 USA- Texas, circa 1982 (Box 15)
    Lady Bird Johnson with LSR, MFR, Nash and Bette Castro, and others; Nimitz Museum.
  - 500,100 USA- Nimitz Museum, 1982 April (Box 15)
    Museum of the Pacific War, Japanese Peace Garden.
  - 500,101 USA- New York and Vermont, 1982 October (Box 15)
    Woodstock mansion, artwork (including bust of JDR Sr.), Philipsburg Manor mill.
  - 500,102 USA- California and New York, 1982 October (Box 15)
    Annenberg Center (Betty Ford Center); Firestone Hall; Pocantico plantings.
  - 500,103 USA- California - Eisenhower Medical Center, 1982 October (Box 15)
  - 500,104 Argentina, 1982 November (Box 15)
    Eastern Air Lines meeting. Riders, Shetland ponies, barbecue.
  - 500,105 Henry Ford Museum and Birthplace, 1983 April (Box 15)
  - 500,106 Vessels, 1950s (Box 15)
    Unidentified sailboat. LSR and others. Includes undated note from Mary Todhunter Rockefeller.
  - 500,106.1 SS United States, 1952 (Box 15)
    In New York harbor. MFR and children on boat alongside. Man sketching on board.
  - 500,107 Europe- England, 1988 May (Box 15)
    Connaught Hotel, London.
  - 500,107.1 Vessels- Models (Box 16)
    Models of Dauntless and Sea Star (Polaroids)
  - 500,108 Vessels- Dauntless, 1950s (Box 16)
  - 500,109 Vessels, Undated (Box 16)
  - 500,110 Vessels- Sea Star, Undated (Box 16)
  - 500,111 Vessels- Sea Star (Virgin Islands), Undated (Box 16)
  - 500,112 Vessels- Evening Star, Undated (Box 16)
    LSR and MFR.
  - 500,113 Vessels- Seasmoke, Undated (Box 16)
  - 500,114 Vessels- Sea Star (Maine), Undated (Box 16)
  - 500,115 Vessels, 1958 February 7 (Box 16)
  - 500,116 Vessels, circa 1970 (Box 16)
  - 500,117 Vessels- Sea Star, 1970 March (Box 16)
    Launch.
  - 500,118 Vessels- Sea Star and Dauntless (Box 16)
    LSR and MFR and others; Hitchcocks.
  - 500,119 Vessels- Sea Star, 1971 February (Box 16)
  - 500,120 Vessels, 1973 April (Box 16)
  - 500,121 Vessels- Sea Star, 1974 November (Box 16)
  - 500,122 Vessels- Sargasso, 1977 March (Box 16)
    La Guaira, Venezuela. LSR, MFR, and others.
  - 500,122.1 Vessels- Dauntless, 1977 October (Box 16)
    Hudson River cruise, LSR, Tom Taxter, Nash Castro, Lady Bird. Includes images of another "Dauntless" boat; helicopter; MFR and Nash Castro on unidentified walkway/bridge. Prints and 27 slides.
  - 500,123 Mauna Kea Hotel and China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Beijing, Forbidden City. (Negatives filed with CS 59-60.)
  - 500,124 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 2- Beijing, Guest House, Zoo and Pandas, LSR and MFR at medical clinic. (Negatives filed with CS 61-62.)
  - 500,126 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 4- Shanghai, Riverboat trip, Bonzai Garden. (Negatives filed with CS 65-66.) Note- Envelope 500,125 not found in file.